That is the toughest spot I
haven't tackled. Would be.
Give me
a hand what do I care now I got to finish
my. Lesson of this letter gentlemen
that ain't for us we're not gentlemen
speak for yourself. Gentlemen this is to
inform you that unless overdue payments
for telling equipment are made within
twenty four hours we will reap
a zest seven Quitman balance now due three
hundred twenty one dollars and eighty
six cents skinflint Finance Corporation
I please I'm president. That put
us out of business but only do you guys
worry about that I'm too young to warrant
it wrinkles on my pretty
little face what we need is
a little music that yourself. Numerous
flashes police are frantically scouring the
town in search of Terry slippery finger
park are going to his round his
eighteenth consecutive state to nine days
a large reward is offered for you after
your car have been Did you ask you does it
burp in the morning try or no burp only
only gasoline containing white carbonate of
soda. Well why don't we take your hog and
collect the reward then we can pay off
bills oh it's just simple it's all
a hog and it's going to walk right in the
air and let you capture you know not
we're going to be paupers part for him
are you kidding we're not even married.
Don't you be quiet all right.
Well anyway I'm going to. A
little home. Oh my head I
can't think when I'm hungry.
Oh if only man had time like
yo look at I still. Want
to run I built baby serves me.
Well I.
Yeah. How do you.
Know you're going to rush out to get the
right answer again Russian All right all
right but why are they I think I'm up on
the fray what your daughter I didn't touch
on.
There already have
a press those. On your team laugh. If
you. Call all.
The all.
Oh oh.
You don't cross at. All.
Oh oh oh oh. oh
Why did you come out of code you know. I'm
sorry oh oh I think nothing of it home
Keith thanks for your welcome.
I am the I'm here I'm sorry
you stepped into me.
And. OK I'm. OK if you.
Want to really come to the right place
you bet this is the stall where you have
dollars have more sense to say we've got
a very short coat you're
looking for I don't want
a cold listen Mr We're going to
give you off we need you have
a get this mess I want to hear oh what
a beautiful Mr Pease. Here is the
beauty to anyone employed smell the ocean
and it's two hundred percent wool two
hundred percent can be he
played a double life not
a good ride and Larry and I know you're
right when you say I don't want to color I
don't want our coat I don't want to oh you
don't want to oh well he wants the pair
of us three black men to tell me the man
wants like get him slack. I don't want any
are not now not in this time of
the customer is always right.
You are rather look like twenty one of
us oh yes trying right on with. The
key office that we don't want your birds
rely you just put Terry are going to buy
property quite right through my hands are
you my employees off I got six White took
a doctor's office and there was nobody
came in here let me down the neighborhood
Well I'll be back right. Now I just
dandy. Listen carefully my
clothes are in the Boy tell us
shop around the corner now when
the watch of the crowd there's
a piece of paper with
a combination to his say I want to do
that job tonight and I need that paper OK
just leave it to me.
And publish. What it was when I found
the pocket of the spams. L.O.L.
Already one to me. One.
Left one right one this is the
combination of what shape.
TH I wonder what that means we
developed you know wrong quiz kid th
th I got it I got it not common headed.
Why didn't you dumb bell stop.
Every hug and tell me how good he was here
the bank robber your crazy that was what
was came up one of the
dummies I know quite. Oh.
I am proud of is my code all
good just a bit oh. Right
a minute brush them off. At least
thirty one inches very thirty one.
Made out of my mother I thought so I know
you're all set right well so you're on
payday right.
But kind of crushing you around
here you had only page. Yes
ma'am and I could act as natural expression.
I'm going to be you I'd like to have
this dress what color had a collar you
mean and a collar and all that a T.
And a hen kind of a brown
reddish I never read
a brown reddish IMO although I
did put in a court coat out
a pair of slacks from my brother they're
the exactly what I want you to have it.
Table got to be. How much of that be forty
you have Monday night but I add that up
. What's the total.
For the modem dollars but there's
a sale today you can be sent off
to forty to fifty OK or just
a moment I'll be right back.
And
a call of you mean brown reddish all yellow
trying to go cucumber to the world. That
we are.
He said forty to fifty Yeah one hundred
two hundred three hundred four
hundred fifty now you are keep the
check. Aren't we the SAPS we had
a fortune and I am
a little slide through I'm going to show
you all of what we think you. Would want
to.
Look upon and have
a big show you did. Well why it
was my wife is just crazy about the way
you fix this code as you want you to make
me
a pair of pants to match. God
they are not I know you come
through baby. This is it.
I receive payment in full
voice clean is my good dirty.
They even took my bankroll but thirty
crooks Come on boys with no one calling.
Reassume the right way. All
by repaying the pockets.
Yes but we need to be we said we'd like to
have our suits cleaned and pressed while
we wait certainly yes we do. Oh.
All right well that piece of paper was in
my pants pocket you mean the one with the
numbers on it that said I did and the
letters L R R R R R Oh yeah where is it you
have a story of
a wise guy OK fellows make
them talk. OK the. Guy
was the one that always. Did you model.
Right how do you. Think.
Come across with that paper or the paper
yes the paper when your say so there it is
.
Well. Look.
Where in the paper I tell you
I have got it. You fought.
For
a high wire in that piece I
got it off I don't want to. I
didn't mean it I didn't
mean that you noble.
Oh is that
a statement. Right
oh my Ari give me your. Oh
oh. Oh come off. Oh. It's hard all right
all right for it already we're in the kid
the moolah now we can pay to get in front
. Oh
a couple more only my phone but I. Wonder
we get our reward the reward off I get
the reward but here's some tickets the
policeman bought tickets to the policeman's
boss.
Range stuff oh OK thanks again Boy
Oh thank you for your kind of.
One hundred two hundred three hundred four
hundred five hundred fifty total How did
it get.